<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on emilygong-zhuying</title>
    <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on emilygong-zhuying</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Opinion Dynamics (REU Project)</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/opiniondynamics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/opiniondynamics/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m participating in the Computational and Applied Mathematics REU (Research Experience for Undergraduates), funded by the NSF, this summer. I collaborate with a team of 4 to conduct research, design 10+ experiments, optimize code, and create visualizations. We simulate Opinions Dynamics in a mathematical network with an adaptive Deffuant–Weisbuch model in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Summarization</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/textsummarization/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/textsummarization/</guid>
      <description>I worked with a team of 8 and implemented extractive text summarization with TF-IDF from scratch and with sklearn. Feel free to check out our GitHub, Streamlit demo, and Medium article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Analysis with Social Media (Weibo)</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/weibo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/weibo/</guid>
      <description>I worked with Professor Mason Porter from UCLA&amp;rsquo;s Math Department on social network analysis, where I modeled a network to examine online community sentiment and behaviors (45k+ posts) under COVID lockdown. After extracting posts through requests and API, I conducted EDA and modeled the network using NetworkX. To examine users&amp;rsquo; sentiments, I developed a deep learning sentiment analysis model for Mandarin Chinese text and achieved an 80+% accuracy.
Check out my research proposal here or take a peek at my code base here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superlinearity of Protests</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/protests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/protests/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m working with Professor Steinert-Threlkeld from UCLA&amp;rsquo;s Public Affairs department to analyze if a superlinearity exists between city population and protest sizes. We are using ACLED dataset for protests across the world and Geonames for population. So far, no correlation has been found between the 2 variables.
Feel free to check out the GitHub repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Forcasting for Oil Prices</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/timeseries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/timeseries/</guid>
      <description>In this project, I explored Oil Prices for the past 6 years (source) utilizing ARIMA and an state-of-the-art time series linear model.
Check out my presentation here for to see the results. My ARIMA model achieved an MSE of 5.88 and &amp;lt; 0.01 for LSTF.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the code for ARIMA models: GitHub repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring K-pop and BTS Song Popularity with Spotify Audio Features &amp; Song Lyrics</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/bts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 12:14:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/bts/</guid>
      <description>In this group project I led, we tried to predict K-Pop song’s popularity through machine learning and natural language processing.
We were first inspired by the BTS 147 Songs Audio Features (Spotify) dataset from Kaggle, but to conduct our analysis, we referred to the following two datasets: the Kpop Artists and Full Spotify Discography and BTS Lyrics dataset (more details in later sections).
Before proceeding, we extracted the “Popularity” scores Spotify generated for each song we observed through the Spotify API and appended it to the datasets mentioned above.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
