<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>emilygong-zhuying</title>
    <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on emilygong-zhuying</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Network Analysis with Social Media (Weibo)</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/weibo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/weibo/</guid>
      <description>I worked with Professor Mason Porter from UCLA&amp;rsquo;s Math Department on social network analysis, where I modeled a network to examine online community sentiment and behaviors (45k+ posts) under COVID lockdown. After extracting posts through requests and API, I conducted EDA and modeled the network using NetworkX. To examine users&amp;rsquo; sentiments, I developed a deep learning sentiment analysis model for Mandarin Chinese text and achieved an 80+% accuracy.
Check out my research proposal here or take a peek at my code base here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superlinearity of Protests</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/protests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/protests/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m working with Professor Steinert-Threlkeld from UCLA&amp;rsquo;s Public Affairs department to analyze if a superlinearity exists between city population and protest sizes. We are using ACLED dataset for protests across the world and Geonames for population. So far, no correlation has been found between the 2 variables.
Feel free to check out the gitHub repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Forcasting for Oil Prices</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/timeseries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/timeseries/</guid>
      <description>In this project, I explored Oil Prices for the past 6 years (source) utilizing ARIMA and an state-of-the-art time series linear model.
Check out my presentation here for to see the results. My ARIMA model achieved an MSE of 5.88 and &amp;lt; 0.01 for LSTF.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the code for ARIMA models: gitHub repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🛠 How to Use Shortcodes?</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/tutorials/shortcode/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 11:37:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/tutorials/shortcode/</guid>
      <description>What is a shortcode? It&amp;rsquo;s basically a block-level html code; you can write shortcodes yourself and find ones online that others have written for you. You have two sets of curly braces and a set of angle brackets { { &amp;lt; short code &amp;gt; } }. (For some reason the website won&amp;rsquo;t compile if I actually type it out correctly, which is without the spaces between each symbols.) Some shortcodes have opening and closing tags like html and some do not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 19:30:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey, welcome to my website! My name is Emily Gong, a third year studying Math of Computation and Linguistics at UCLA. I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about data science, machine learning, and project/product management. You can find me on GitHub, LinkedIn, or through Email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎧 How to Fetch Data through the Spotify API</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/tutorials/spotifyapi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 18:46:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/tutorials/spotifyapi/</guid>
      <description>coming soon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>💡 How to Make a Hugo Website</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/tutorials/hugowebsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 18:45:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/tutorials/hugowebsite/</guid>
      <description>Why building a website with Hugo? In short, it&amp;rsquo;s a really fast and simple way to have a static website to yourself, through which you can display your recent projects, share your thoughts, and have fun with it.
Before we officially start&amp;hellip; The tutorial is based on macOS and I&amp;rsquo;m using GitHub Pages for deployment.
Tools you&amp;rsquo;ll need Terminal A text editor like VSCode A GitHub account hugo Setting up Open your terminal - easy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring K-pop and BTS Song Popularity with Spotify Audio Features &amp; Song Lyrics</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/bts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 12:14:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/projects/bts/</guid>
      <description>In this group project I led, we tried to predict K-Pop song’s popularity through machine learning and natural language processing.
We were first inspired by the BTS 147 Songs Audio Features (Spotify) dataset from Kaggle, but to conduct our analysis, we referred to the following two datasets: the Kpop Artists and Full Spotify Discography and BTS Lyrics dataset (more details in later sections).
Before proceeding, we extracted the “Popularity” scores Spotify generated for each song we observed through the Spotify API and appended it to the datasets mentioned above.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/personal/firstblog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 12:13:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilygong-zhuying.github.io/personal/firstblog/</guid>
      <description>This is my first time building a website and I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to add more fun stuff to it, like my data science projects, some design projects, and maybe some drawing + photography? We will see ;)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
